MENU

Privacy Policy
==============

ROOT/Northwest Sports Privacy Policy

Last updated: January 12th, 2024

Thank you for visiting ROOT SPORTS Northwest, a service owned by NW Sports Net LLC (“NWSN”). NWSN is referred to in this document as “we” or “us” or “our.” This Privacy Policy explains information practices and choices you can make about information collected through our websites, applications (“apps”), services, connected devices (e.g., connected TVs), and other offerings (each a “Site” or collectively, the “Sites”). This Privacy Policy applies to any Site that links directly to this Privacy Policy. For certain offerings on our Sites, there may be additional notices about our information practices and choices. Please read those additional privacy disclosures to understand how they apply to you. Our Privacy Policy is designed to provide transparency into our privacy practices and principles.

**INFORMATION WE COLLECT**

We may collect different types of information during your interactions with our Sites and through our advertising and media across the Internet and mobile apps. This information may include personal information (e.g., name, phone number, postal address, email address, and certain payment information), technical information (e.g., device identifier, IP address, browser type, operating system) and usage information (e.g., how you use and navigate to and from our Sites, and information about content or advertisements you have been shown or have clicked on). We may combine these types of information together, and collectively refer to all of this information in this Privacy Policy as “Information.” Information may be collected as described below and through the use of cookies, web beacons, pixels, and other similar technologies by us or by other companies on our behalf. Below we describe the types of Information we may collect:

**Registration, account, and sign-up information.** We may collect Information in the course of your use of, or registration with, our Sites. For example, when you create an account, register for or download an app, or sign-up for a product or service, you may provide us with certain personal information. This type of personal information may include name, phone number, postal address, fax number, email address, or certain payment information (e.g., billing and transaction information). We may also collect Information about your interest in and use of various products, programs, services, and content available on or through our Sites.

**Other information you provide.** When you interact with our Sites, you may share other information about yourself by, for example, publishing and sharing the information with the Site’s website or in the Site’s community, creating a or profile, or filing out a survey or application. Sometimes you may also choose to provide more sensitive forms of personal information to us, such as information regarding your physical or mental health, biometric data, race or ethnicity, religious or philosophical beliefs, sexual orientation, political opinions, or trade union membership. For example, we may collect this type of sensitive information if you participate in surveys, contests, focus groups, or opportunities to test new products, programs, or services. We collect this sensitive information with your consent, if required by law, and we take steps to protect and limit any use of it to the purposes for which it is provided. We may use third party service providers and/or third-party software to record voice or text chat to help address customer service inquiries.

**Information from others; inviting friends.** On some of our Sites we may collect Information other people submit about you. For example, a friend might submit Information to invite you to participate in an offering, make recommendations, or share content. By processing these requests, we may receive your Information, including a recipient’s name, postal address, email address, telephone number, or information about your interest in and use of various products, programs, services, and content. Some of our Sites also allow users to invite friends to participate in activities by providing their friends’ contact details or importing contacts from your address book or from other sites.

**Information from other sources.** On occasion, we combine Information with other online information we receive, including usage information about your interactions with other websites and with online advertising and media. We also supplement or combine Information with Information from a variety of other sources or outside records, including third-party data providers that provide us with Information such as demographics, transaction and purchase history, Information about the content and advertisements you interact with, or inferences about your demographics or preferences. We may receive Information from third parties with which you have a subscription agreement that includes access to our content or services, such as a cable or smart device provider.

**Information you provide through social media.** You can engage with some of our content and offerings, such as videos, games, apps, and other offerings on or through third party communities, forums, and social media sites, platforms, services, plug-ins, and applications (“Social Media Sites”). When you link to or interact with our Sites, content, or offerings through Social Media Sites, you may allow us to receive certain Information from your social media account (e.g., name, user ID, email address, profile photo, photos and videos, gender, birthday, location, your friends and their contact details, people you follow and/or who follow you, posts, ‘likes’,  and other user-generated content). We may also receive Information from your interaction with our content (e.g., content viewed, game performance, high scores, and information about advertisements you have been shown or have clicked on). By providing this Information or otherwise interacting with our Sites through Social Media Sites, you consent to our use of Information from the Social Media Sites in accordance with this Privacy Policy. For information about how you can customize your privacy settings on Social Media Sites, and how those Social Media Sites handle your personal information and content, please refer to their privacy help guides, privacy policies, and terms of use.

**Information you provide through public forums.** If you post or share Information or content, such as photos, letters, videos, or comments, while participating in online forums on our Sites, or when you interact with our Sites through Social Media Sites, depending on your privacy settings, this Information or content and your username may become public on the Internet or within a community of users. We cannot prevent further use of this Information once you share it in a publicly available forum. For information about how you can customize your privacy settings on Social Media Sites, and how those Social Media Sites handle your personal information and content, please refer to their privacy help guides, privacy policies, and terms of use. To protect users on our own Sites, we may use third party service providers and/or third-party software to moderate chat among our users. These moderation services may include recordings of text or voice chat for purposes of avoiding or addressing potential abuses of our terms of use or other concerns on behalf of our users.

**Location information.** We may have access to certain Information about your location, such as your country or address, when you provide it either directly or via device information. If you access our Sites on your mobile device, we may collect Information about your device’s precise location. We also may derive a general location from device information (such as an IP address).

**Event Information**, including images and clips, whether captured via technology, such as a photo booth or by other means, by us or a third party on our behalf, and other Information relating to participation in the event, such as food allergies and other individual requirements.

**Video and streaming information.** For some Sites, we collect information about the films, TV shows, and videos that you view. For example, if you stream video content using our Sites, we may collect information about your interaction with that content or service, such as the title and genre, watchlists you compile, and searches you conduct, duration and number of streams and downloads and system information related to streaming and download quality.

**Technical and usage information.** We also collect certain technical and usage information when you use our Sites, such as the type of device, browser, and operating system you are using, accounts you use or link together, your Internet service provider or mobile carrier, unique device identifier, IDFA or IDFV, MAC address, IP address, device and browser settings, the webpages and apps you use, advertisements you see and interact with, and certain Site usage information. See our Cookies and Other Technical Information section for more information on how we may use these technologies to collect this Information. We may use service providers or other solutions to record users’ interactions with our Sites, which may include mouse clicks, mouse movements, page scrolling, and keystrokes/key touches during those sessions. We typically use these recordings to diagnose issues, identify areas for improvement for our sites, and encourage further engagement with our sites.

**HOW WE USE THE INFORMATION**

We use Information for the purposes described in this Privacy Policy or disclosed at the time of collection or with your consent.

**Providing and marketing products and services.** We may use the Information we collect about you through our Sites to fulfill your requests for, and otherwise provide or analyze your use of our products, programs, services and content, to facilitate sharing and other interactions with Social Media Sites, and to provide, develop, maintain, personalize, protect, and improve your experience and our offerings. For example, we use Information we collect to enable you to do things like (i) watch trailers, movies, programs, games and video clips, (ii) get entertainment or sports news and updates, (iii) get information about our products, programs, services, and content, (iv) locate and access personalized information or functionality based on your interests or location (e.g., find stores, theaters, sporting events or show times), (v) buy digital content, movie tickets, or other purchases, (vi) play games, (vii) engage with interactive features, activities, and Social Media Sites, (viii) read and post comments, content, and reviews, (ix) fill out surveys or provide feedback, or (x) enter promotions, contests, and sweepstakes. We may also use Information to offer, market, and advertise products, programs, and services from us and our affiliates, business partners, and select third parties that we believe may be of interest to you or assess features of a Site and options to encourage more engagement. Information you provide on one Site may be used to provide targeted marketing and/or advertising on another Site.

**Communicating with you and others.** We may use Information about you to communicate with you, such as (i) to notify you when you win one of our contests or sweepstakes or when we make changes to our policies or user agreements, (ii) to respond to your inquiries and provide you with customer service, (iii) to communicate with you about your purchases or transactions, (iv) to contact you about your account, or (v) to send you information about promotions, offerings, and Site features. You may also choose to receive push notifications from us on your mobile device. If you choose to submit content for publication online or in other forums, we may publish your screen name or username and other Information you have provided to us on our Sites, the Internet, or elsewhere. We use Information that you provide about others to enable us to send them invitations, promotions, or other content on your behalf or through our Sites. From time to time, we also may use this Information to offer, market, or advertise products, programs, or services to them from us and our affiliates, and business partners.

**Use of technical and usage information.** We may use technical and usage information to improve the design, functionality and content of our Sites and to enable us to personalize your experience with our Sites and offerings. For example, we may use this Information (i) to provide, develop, maintain, personalize, protect, and improve our Sites, products, programs, and services and to operate our business, (ii) to perform analytics, including to analyze and report on usage and performance of our Sites, (iii) to protect against, identify, and prevent fraud and other unlawful activity, (iv) to create aggregate data about groups or categories of our users, and (iv) for us and our affiliates, business partners, and select third parties to target, offer, market, or advertise products, programs, or services.

**Compliance.** We may use Information we collect to detect, investigate, and prevent activities on our Sites that may violate our terms of use, could be fraudulent, violate copyright, or other rules or that may be otherwise illegal, to comply with legal requirements, and to protect our rights and the rights and safety of our users and others.

**INFORMATION SHARING AND DISCLOSURE**

We may share and disclose Information in the following ways or for any other purpose disclosed at the time of collection:

**With your consent**. We may disclose Information when you provide us with your consent to do so.

**Legal and law enforcement purposes**. We may disclose Information in response to legal process, for example in response to a court order or a subpoena, or in response to a law enforcement agency’s request. We also may disclose such Information to third parties: (i) in connection with fraud prevention activities, (ii) where we believe it is necessary to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, (iii) in situations that may involve violations of our terms of use or other rules, (iv) to protect our rights and the rights and safety of others, and (v) as otherwise required by law.

**Change of control**. We may transfer Information in the event of a business transaction, such as if we or one of our business units or our relevant assets are acquired by, sold to, or merged with another company or as part of a bankruptcy proceeding or a business reorganization.

**Service providers**. Organizations that perform services for us may have access to Information to help carry out the services they are performing for us, such as, but not limited to, creation, maintenance, hosting, and delivery of our Sites, products, and services, conduct marketing, handle payments, email and order fulfillment, administer contests, conduct research and analytics, or customer service.

**Affiliates**. We may disclose Information to affiliates. For example, we may share Information we collect with our affiliates to provide, improve, offer, market, and otherwise communicate with you about their own products and services. Our products and services may be developed, managed, marketed and sold by a variety of our affiliates. Public recognition may derive from, for example, use of common branding elements, advertising, press, social media reports or other public form of notice. We require the affiliate to protect the Information consistent with this Privacy Policy. We may also combine Information that identifies you personally with data that comes from an affiliate that has a different privacy policy. When we do that, our Privacy Policy applies to the combined data set.

**Business partners and third parties**. We may also share Information with business partners and third parties (e.g., other companies, retailers, research organizations, advertisers, ad agencies, advertising networks and platforms, participatory databases, publishers, and non-profit organizations) that may want to market products or services to you. If we share personal information with such unaffiliated third parties for their own marketing purposes, we provide you with an opportunity to opt out of such uses either at the point of collection or through the choice mechanisms set forth in this Privacy Policy. To learn more about your choices, please see our Your Choices and Controls section below.

**Linked sites**. Some of our Sites contain links to other sites, including Social Media Sites, whose information practices may be different from ours. Information you submit to other sites will be governed by the other sites’ privacy policies and terms.

**Sponsors and co-promotions**. We may sometimes offer content or programs (e.g., contests, sweepstakes, promotions, games, applications or Social Media Site integrations) that are sponsored by or co-branded with identified third parties. By virtue of these relationships, the sponsoring or co-branding parties may collect or obtain Information from visitors that participate in the activity. We have no control over these sponsoring or co-branding parties’ use of this Information. We encourage you to visit the privacy policy of any such sponsoring or co-branding party to learn about their data practices prior to providing Information through sponsored or co-branded content or programs.

**Advertising networks**. We may share certain information with parties to provide advertising to you based on your interests. For more information, please see our Ad Choices section below.

**YOUR CHOICES AND CONTROLS**

**Marketing communications and sharing with third parties**. We provide you with an opportunity to express your preferences with respect to receiving certain marketing communications from us, and our sharing of personal information with unaffiliated third parties for their direct marketing purposes. If you ever decide in the future that you would like to update these preferences, you may (i) log in to an account you have created with us at one of our Site to adjust your settings, if available, or (ii) send us an email at [NWSNprivacy@rootsportsnw.com](mailto:NWSNprivacy@rootsportsnw.com). To opt out of receiving our email marketing communications, you can follow the “unsubscribe” instructions provided tin any marketing email you receive from us.  If you previously chose to receive push notifications on your mobile device from us, but no longer wish to receive them, you can manage your preferences through your device or app settings, depending on the type of device. If you have signed up to receive text messages from us and no longer wish to receive such messages, you may follow the instructions to stop the delivery of such messages, which may include by replying “STOP” to the received text message.

**Ad Choices**. On our own or working with affiliates or third parties, we may present advertisements and engage in data collection, reporting, ad delivery and response measurement, and site analytics on our Sites and on third party websites across the Internet and applications over time. We, our affiliates, or third parties may use cookies, web beacons, pixels, software development kits (“SDKs”) or similar technologies to collect information across websites, services, and apps over time to perform this activity. We, our affiliates, or third parties may use and transfer this information, including third party information, to help serve advertising that may be more relevant to your interests on and off our Sites and across your devices and browsers. This type of advertising is known as “interest-based advertising” or “targeted advertising”. We, our affiliates, or third parties may also use this information to associate your different browsers and devices together for interest-based advertising and for other purposes like research, analytics, internal operations, fraud prevention, and enhancing consumer experiences.

For more information about interest-based or targeted advertising on your desktop or mobile browser, and to opt out of this type of advertising by third parties that participate in self-regulatory programs, please visit the Network Advertising Initiative website  ([https://www.networkadvertising.org/understanding-online-advertising/what-are-my-options](https://www.networkadvertising.org/understanding-online-advertising/what-are-my-options)) and/or the Digital Advertising Alliance (“DAA”) Self-Regulatory Program for Online Behavioral Advertising website ([https://www.networkadvertising.org/understanding-online-advertising/what-are-my-options](https://www.networkadvertising.org/understanding-online-advertising/what-are-my-options)).

To learn more about interest-based or targeted advertising in mobile apps and to opt out of this type of advertising by third parties that participate in the DAA’s AppChoices tool, please use this link to download the version of AppChoices for your device ([https://youradchoices.com/appchoices](https://youradchoices.com/appchoices)).  Please note that any opt-out choice you exercise through these programs will apply to interest-based or targeted advertising by the third parties you select, but will still allow the collection of data for other purposes, including research, analytics, and internal operations. You may continue to receive advertising, but that advertising may be less relevant to your interests.

You may have options to opt out of our own collection, use, and transfer of data as described above for interested based advertising depending on your mobile device and operating system. For example, most device operating systems (e.g., iOS for Apple phones, Android for Android devices, and Windows for Microsoft devices) provide their own instructions on how to limit or prevent the delivery of tailored in-application advertisements. You may review the support materials and/or the privacy settings for the respective operating systems to learn more about these features and how they apply to tailored in-app advertisements.

**Precise location information**. To disable the collection of precise location information from your mobile device through our mobile apps, you can access your mobile device settings and choose to limit that collection.

See also our Cookies and Other Technical Information section for more choices about managing other technical and usage information.

**COOKIES AND OTHER TECHNICAL INFORMATION**

**Cookies and other technologies**. We, and our affiliates, vendors, and business partners may send “cookies” to your computer or use similar technologies to understand and enhance your online experience at our Sites and through our advertising and media across the Internet and mobile apps.

We may use these technologies to help recognize your browser or device, maintain your preferences, provide certain Site features, and collect Information about interactions with our Sites, our content, and our communications. For example, when corresponding with you via HTML capable email, web beacons and other technologies let us know about your activity, including whether you received and opened our email, clicked through a link, or otherwise interacted with our content, and this information may be associated with Information previously collected.

We may also use these other technologies (i) to provide, develop, maintain, personalize, protect, and improve our Sites, products, programs, and services and to operate our business, (ii) to perform analytics, including to analyze and report on usage and performance of our Sites and marketing materials, (iii) to protect against, identify, and prevent fraud and other unlawful activity, (iv) to create aggregate data about groups or categories of our users, (v) to synchronize users across devices, affiliates, business partners, and select third parties, and (vi) for us and our affiliates, business partners, and select third parties to target, offer, market, or advertise products, programs, or services. These technologies also facilitate, manage, and measure the performance of targeted advertisements displayed on or delivered by or through us and/or other networks or sites. By visiting the Site, whether as a registered user or otherwise, you acknowledge, and agree that you are giving us your consent to track your activities and your use of the Site through the technologies described above, as well as similar technologies developed in the future, and that we may use such tracking technologies in the emails we send to you.

**Managing cookies and other technologies**. These technologies can either be persistent (i.e., they remain on your computer until you delete them) or temporary (i.e., they last only until you close your browser). Check your browser settings to learn how to delete cookies and other tracking technologies.

You may adjust your browser to reject cookies from us or from any other website. Controlling cookies via browser controls may not limit our use of other technologies. Please consult your browser’s settings for more information. However, blocking these technologies might prevent you from accessing some of our content or Site features.

Some of our Sites may use locally stored objects (“LSOs”) to provide certain content, such as video on demand, video clips, or animation, and a better user experience. Adobe’s Flash player and similar applications use this technology to remember settings, preferences, and usage similar to browser cookies. Flash cookies are not managed through your web browser, but you can access your Flash management tools by visiting Adobe’s web site. Your browser may also offer other tools to delete or reject other LSOs; please check your browser’s settings or help menu for more information.

Some of our sites may use Google Analytics to analyze traffic. You can find out more information about [Google Analytics cookies](https://developers.google.com/analytics/devguides/collection/analyticsjs/cookie-usage) by visiting the following location provided: [https://developers.google.com/analytics/devguides/collection/analyticsjs/cookie-usage](https://developers.google.com/analytics/devguides/collection/analyticsjs/cookie-usage). To opt out of Google Analytics relating to your use of our Sites, you can download and install the [Browser Plugin](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en) available by visiting the following location provided: [https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en).

Some Sites may feature Nielsen proprietary measurement software, which will allow users to contribute to market research, such as Nielsen TV Ratings. To learn more about the information that Nielsen software may collect and your choices, please see the [Nielsen Digital Measurement Privacy Policy](https://www.nielsen.com/us/en/legal/privacy-statement/digital-measurement/) by visiting the following location provided: [https://www.nielsen.com/us/en/legal/privacy-statement/digital-measurement/](https://www.nielsen.com/us/en/legal/privacy-statement/digital-measurement/).

See the Your Choices and Controls section to learn how to control data collection for certain purposes.

**INFORMATION SECURITY**

We have put in place reasonable controls designed to help safeguard the personal information we collect via the Sites. However, no security measures are perfect, and we cannot assure you that personal information that we collect will never be accessed or used in an unauthorized way.

**HOW YOU CAN ACCESS, DELETE, OR CORRECT INFORMATION**

To access, delete, or correct personal information that we have collected about you online from Sites on which this Privacy Policy is posted, please log into your account if you have created one with us. Residents of some US states have specific rights relating to access, deletion, and correction requests. Please visit the [California & Other US States Rights](https://www.warnermediaprivacy.com/policycenter/b2c/CA-rights/en-us) Supplement below for a description of those state-specific rights.

**INTERNATIONAL TRANSFER**

We operate internationally, and many of our computer systems are currently based in the United States, which means Information we collect will be processed by us in the U.S. where data protection and privacy regulations may not offer the same level of protection as in other parts of the world, such as the European Union. If you use or visit our Sites from outside the United States, you consent to the collection and/or processing in the United States of Information we collect from you.

**CALIFORNIA & OTHER US STATES RIGHTS**

Some US states, such as California and Virginia, require us to inform their residents about additional privacy information and rights. Please visit our [California & Other US States Right Supplement](https://www.warnermediaprivacy.com/policycenter/b2c/CA-rights/en-us) which provides this additional privacy information and explains those additional rights.

**NOTIFICATION REGARDING PRIVACY POLICY UPDATES**

From time to time, we may update this Privacy Policy. We will notify you about material changes to this Privacy Policy by placing a notice on our Sites. We encourage you to periodically check back and review this Privacy Policy so that you always know our current privacy practices.

**HOW TO CONTACT US**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy you may contact us at: [https://northwest.rootsports.com/contact-us/](https://northwest.rootsports.com/contact-us/) or by phone: 425-641-0104, via email:[NWSNprivacy@rootsportsnw.com](mailto:NWSNprivacy@rootsportsnw.com)  or via mail: NW Sports Net LLC, 3626 156th Ave. SE,  Bellevue, WA 98006

**SUPPLEMENT**

**CALIFORNIA & OTHER STATES RIGHTS**

Some US states, such as California and Virginia, require us to inform their residents about additional privacy information and rights. This supplement (“US State Supplement”) to our Privacy Policy provides this additional privacy information and explains those additional US state rights. This US State Supplement applies to our online and offline practices.

**Categories of Personal Information We Collect and Share**

**Here are the categories of personal information that we may collect and process:**

* Identifiers – such as name, phone number, postal address, zip code, email address, account name or number, or other similar identifiers
* Legally Protected Characteristics – such as age or gender
* Unique and other online identifiers – such as IP address, device IDs, or other similar identifiers that relate to your device and its operating system
* Customer records and other commercial information – such as products or services purchased, obtained, or considered, or other purchasing or consuming histories or tendencies
* Internet or other electronic network activity information – such as browsing history, search history, and information regarding your interactions with our websites, applications (“apps”), ads, content, services, connected devices (e.g., connected TVs), and other offerings (each a “Site” or collectively, the “Sites”).
* Biometric information – if you choose to participate in one of our interactive research studies or other initiatives
* Audio, electronic, visual, thermal, olfactory, or similar information – such as photos, videos and video footage (CCTV), or recordings that you choose to post to our Sites or otherwise provide to us while using our Sites
* Geolocation information – such as your device’s general location in connection with the Platform
* Inferences or audience segmentation – such as individual profiles, preferences, characteristics, and behaviors
* “Sensitive Personal Information,” such as:
    * Social security, driver’s license, state identification card, or passport number, account log-in, or a financial account, debit card, or credit card number in combination with any required security or access code, password, or credentials allowing access to an account
    * Precise geolocation
    * Racial or ethnic origin, religious or philosophical beliefs, or union membership
    * Health information
    * Information regarding sexual orientation
    * Information regarding citizenship or immigration status
    * Information we know pertains to a child under 13

**We may collect, share, sell, or otherwise process these categories of personal information, including Sensitive Personal Information, for the following business or commercial purposes:**

* Providing products or services you request and performing services on behalf of the business, such as customer service, processing or fulfilling orders, providing content recommendations, and processing payments
* Maintaining or servicing accounts
* Auditing customer transactions and other internal risk management or compliance purposes
* Prevention of fraud, crime, and other harms, providing security, and protecting the integrity of our Sites, products, or business
* Debugging or repairing or debugging systems or Sites, including to deliver intended functionality
* Marketing and advertising, including targeted advertising
* Internal research, analytics and development – e.g., user-preference analytics
* Developing, maintaining, provisioning or upgrading networks, products, services, or devices

**We may obtain personal information from a variety of sources, including:**

* Directly from you – such as information you provide when you register or sign-up for our Sites or services and technical and usage information when you use our or our affiliates’ Sites or services
* Our joint ventures and promotional and strategic partners
* Information suppliers and other unaffiliated third parties, such as linked sites, third-party platforms, Social Media Sites and marketing mailing lists
* Distributors and other vendors
* Other users who submit information about you – such as to invite you to participate in an offering, make recommendations, or share content
* Publicly available sources

**Retention of personal information:**

We retain personal information only for so long as reasonably needed to fulfill the purposes for which we collected or obtained it. We use reasonable business criteria to establish retention periods for personal information. For example, if you register on our Sites, we will store your personal information for as long as needed to maintain your account, fulfill your requests, enforce any applicable terms that govern your use of the Sites, maintain appropriate records of the above, or as otherwise required by law.

Disclosures of personal information, including sales or sharing of personal information to third parties

**We may disclose, for a business purpose, the following categories of personal information to third parties:**

* Identifiers
* Characteristics of protected classifications
* Unique and other online identifiers
* Customer Records and commercial information
* Internet or other electronic network activity information
* Biometric information
* Audio, electronic, visual, thermal, olfactory, or similar information
* Geolocation Data
* Government identifiers
* Health information
* Inferences or audience segmentation
* Sensitive Personal Information

**We may disclose, for a business purpose, each of those categories of personal information to the following categories of third parties:**

* Affiliated Entities – These entities are associated with us through common ownership.
* Service Providers – These entities process information on our behalf for business purposes, helping us provide products or services to you
* Social Media Platforms – These entities maintain networks connecting individuals and organizations – such as Facebook, LinkedIn, or Twitter
* Advertising Partners – These entities help us advertise our products or services, as well as connect us with others who want to place advertisements on some of our products or services
* Analytics Partners – These entities help us collect data on how our products or services are used, so that we can improve them and better understand our consumers
* Promotional Partners – We partner with these entities to jointly promote our products, for example by running sweepstakes, contests or other promotional campaigns
* Government Entities – These entities include law enforcement authorities, regulatory agencies, and courts

**Categories of personal information shared with or sold to third parties**

We do not disclose personal information to third parties in exchange for monetary consideration (e.g., cash payment). However, California law defines ‘sale’ very broadly. It includes the disclosure of personal information in exchange for anything of value. California law also defines “sharing” to mean disclosure of personal information for targeted advertising.

**Applying these definitions, we may have previously sold or shared the following categories of personal information to third parties:**

* Identifiers
* Characteristics of protected classifications
* Unique and other online identifiers
* Customer Records and commercial information
* Internet or other electronic network activity information
* Biometric information
* Audio, electronic, visual, thermal, olfactory, or similar information
* Geolocation Data
* Government identifiers
* Health information
* Inferences or audience segmentation
* Sensitive Personal Information

**We may have sold or shared each of these categories of personal information to the following categories of third parties:**

* Affiliated Entities
* Social Media Platforms
* Advertising Partners
* Analytics Partners
* Promotional Partners

**YOUR STATE SPECIFIC RIGHTS**

This section describes some of the state-specific privacy rights that are available to residents of the states that were mentioned at the beginning of this US State Supplement. When you make a request, we may provide more detailed information regarding whether your request is subject to applicable law, and whether any exception or limitation applies.

**YOUR RIGHT TO ASK US TO DELETE YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION**

Upon your request, we will delete the personal information we have collected about you, subject to certain legally permissible exceptions.

To make a request, please send us an email at NWSNprivacy@rootsportsnw.com.

**YOUR RIGHT TO ASK US TO ACCESS YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION**

You have the right to ask us to confirm that we process your personal information, or to ask us for a copy of the specific personal information we have collected about you.

To make a request, please send us an email at NWSNprivacy@rootsportsnw.com.

In addition, if you are a California resident, you have the right to request certain information about our practices in the prior 12 months with respect to personal information. In particular, you can request the following:

* The categories of personal information that we’ve collected
* The categories of sources from which we collected personal information
* The business or commercial purposes for which we collected or sold personal information

You can submit a request to us for the following additional information:

* The categories of third parties to which we’ve shared or sold personal information, and the category or categories of personal information shared or sold to each
* The categories of third parties to which we’ve disclosed personal information, and the category or categories of personal information disclosed to each

**YOUR RIGHT TO ASK US NOT TO SELL OR SHARE YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION – CALIFORNIA**

If you are a California resident, you can tell us not to sell or share (defined by California law to mean that we have disclosed personal information to a third party in exchange for anything of value or for targeted online advertising based on your activities over time across other websites and applications), your personal information according to applicable law, by sending us an email at NWSNprivacy@rootsportsnw.com. **This option is limited to California residents.**

California has specific rules regarding the use of California Information from consumers under 16 years of age.  In particular,  if we knowingly collect the California Information of a consumer under the age of 16, we will not share or sell the information unless we receive affirmative permission to do so.  If the consumer is between the ages of 13 and 16 years of age, the consumer may provide that permission; if the consumer is under the age of 13, the consumer’s parent or guardian must provide the permission.

**YOUR RIGHT TO LIMIT OUR USE OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION FOR TARGETED ADVERTISING**

You can ask us not to use your personal information for targeted online advertising, which means we will not use personal information collected by third parties from your activities over time across websites and applications we do not operate to present ads that we think will interest you. Even if you opt out of targeted ads, we will continue to collect and use data for purposes that are not related to targeted advertising, including research, analytics, and internal operations, and to serve you ads based on information we gain from your direct engagement with our content and products. To opt-out of targeted advertising, please review your options set forth in our Privacy Policy.

**YOUR RIGHT TO ASK US TO CORRECT YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION**

You can ask us to correct information about you that is inaccurate. We will take into account the nature of the personal information, where we obtained the personal information, and the purposes of our processing when we address your request. We may deny your request to correct if we determine that these circumstances make it more likely than not that the personal information we have is accurate.

**Some of your information can be updated through settings in our apps and websites. Please check there first.**

If you are unable to correct your information through self-service tools, you may send us an email at NWSNprivacy@rootsportsnw.com.

**YOUR RIGHT TO LIMIT OUR USE OF YOUR SENSITIVE PERSONAL INFORMATION**

We may use Sensitive Personal Information about you for the business or commercial purposes described above.  Subject to a few exceptions, you may limit our use of this Sensitive Personal Information to only uses that are reasonably necessary to perform services or provide goods. Depending on your state, you may have the right to limit our processing of certain Sensitive Personal Information (or to withdraw consent for such processing if you previously gave it).

**YOUR RIGHT TO LIMIT OUR USE OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION FOR PROFILING/AUTOMATED PROCESSING**

Under applicable law, you may have the right to opt-out of certain automated processing performed on personal information to evaluate, analyze, or predict personal aspects of a person’s economic situation, health, personal preferences, interests, reliability, behavior, location, or movements. At this point we are not aware of any such processing that could produce legal or similarly significant effects concerning you. However, if you  have questions or concerns, please contact us at NWSNprivacy@rootsportsnw.com.

**HOW TO EXERCISE YOUR STATE SPECIFIC RIGHTS**

You may exercise any of the rights described in this US State Supplement, by sending us an email at NWSNprivacy@rootsportsnw.com.  These requests are generally free. When you submit a request, we may contact you to confirm the request was not fraudulently submitted.

If you are the parent or guardian of a minor child, you may also submit a request on behalf of your child.  In that event, we will ask you to provide your child’s email address and to submit a signed form authorizing us to proceed with the request regarding your child’s personal information.

You may also designate an authorized agent to submit a request on your behalf.  Depending on the nature of the request, we may authenticate the request, such as by requiring a signed written permission from you that authorizes the agent to act on your behalf. A valid power of attorney will constitute signed written permission, but you are not required to obtain a power of attorney to use an authorized agent.

Your authorized agent can make a request by contacting us at NWSNprivacy@rootsportsnw.com.

**YOUR RIGHT TO APPEAL**

In certain situations, if we deny/cannot fulfill your request, you may appeal the denial by contacting us via NWSNprivacy@rootsportsnw.com to ask us to review your request again.

**OUR SUPPORT FOR THE EXERCISE OF YOUR DATA RIGHTS**

We are committed to providing you control over your personal information. You have the right not to receive discriminatory treatment if you exercise any of the rights explained in this US State Supplement of the Privacy Policy.

**YOUR CALIFORNIA PRIVACY RIGHTS TO REQUEST INFORMATION ABOUT OUR PRACTICES WITH RESPECT TO PERSONAL INFORMATION WE COLLECT AND SHARE ABOUT YOU**

**California Consumers under 16 Years Old**

As of the Effective Date of this US State Supplement, we do not have actual knowledge that we share or sell personal information of consumers under 16 years of age.

**California Consumers Under 18 Years Old**

California Consumers who are registered users of the Sites and under 18 years of age may request removal of content or information they posted on the Sites. We will remove such content or information when we are required to do so by law. To request removal of content or information you posted on the Sites, you may contact us at NWSNprivacy@rootsportsnw.com.

However, even if we remove the content or information that you posted, we cannot completely prevent further use or disclosure of that content or information by others once you have shared it in a publicly available forum.

**CCPA METRICS**

CCPA Regulations require us to provide disclosure of metrics for the previous calendar year regarding certain requests by California residents, which we can provide upon request. These metrics report the number of access, correction, deletion, Limit My Use of Sensitive Personal Information, and Do Not Sell or Share requests we received, the number fulfilled in whole or in part, and the number denied as well as the average number of days in which we substantively responded.

**NOTIFICATION REGARDING UPDATES**

From time to time, we may update this US State Supplement. We will notify you about any material changes by placing a notice on our sites. We encourage you to periodically check back and review this Supplement so that you are up to date.

**HOW TO CONTACT US**

If you have any questions about this US State Supplement, you may contact us at: https://northwest.rootsports.com/contact-us/ or by phone: 425-641-0104, via email: NWSNprivacy@rootsportsnw.com  or via mail: NW Sports Net LLC, 3626 156th Ave. SE,  Bellevue, WA 98006.

© 2024 ROOT SPORTS Powered by [OneCMS™ |](https://www.intertechmedia.com/features/one-cms/?utm_source=footer_link&utm_medium=website "OneCMS™.") Served by [InterTech Media LLC](https://www.intertechmedia.com/?utm_source=footer_link&utm_medium=website "Link to InterTech Media Homepage")

2728133247

Mozilla/5.0 (Linux; Android 8.0; Pixel 2 Build/OPD3.170816.012) AppleWebKit/537.36 (KHTML, like Gecko) Chrome/48.0.3993.1762 Mobile Safari/537.36

a8bcb949c3ba4c8559a0121842f835891e9af8a4

1
